Thank you.
Thank you for the sync.
It's just one camera...
Thank you very much for synchronizing with me.
Well, hello again everyone! The cause is me!
My name is Takato Okura!
I'm Kosaku Koizumi!
Nice to meet you!
Well, let's go! So, this is it.
The cause is you, on March 13th.
On March 13th, we released the concept EP Family Law
I'd like to give you a lecture on how to support the song "Alien" from the point of view of inference.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
I'm going to be doing a lecture on how to support the song "Alien" from a deductive point of view.
I've been thinking about the fact that I'm going to be doing this video with these two guys for the first time in a long time.
I'm going to do a penlight version and Mr. Craft is going to do a clap version.
I'm going to do a penlight version and Kosaku-san is going to do a clap version, so please pay attention to them and enjoy the live performance.
Okay, I'll be right back.
Starter!
Coy is a sweet premonition and unstable gradle, it's all your fault, you've got crazy crazy art in your brain.
It's about time I saw Clay.
I'm thinking of you, love folium choo choo choo
Chew.
This is the important part... the chew.
The choo choo is so important
It's about time for the clap!
Ready
Now here's the hard part! Try your best to remember!
The right one!
Identity!
What's this?
Eyes!
Eye!
It's on!
It's clear.
Right?
Nina nina nina nina.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Ready, crazy! Crazy!
Ready, for you! For you!
Ten.
That's cool.
Seino.
Yes, sir.
Pappa.
Clear.
BUCK-SEE
THREE
Throw
CASE
Gar Games
Mode Games
You are
Pappa
P-pa-pa
Yes, sir.
Ready
Lilililililililililililililililililililililililililililil
Ah!
Yes, ma'am.
Let Masaya listen to you sing
Yes, ma'am
Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
Yes, ma'am.
Whoo-hoo!
Yee-haw.
Okay.
for you for you
Uh...
Yes, sir.
Okay.
joo
It's ready!
Ready!
PAPPA
pappa
p-pa-pa
Pow!
P-p-pa-pa.
You can't give me those synchros and that, too.
Come on, I've already used this until the last minute.
The last one. If it's the last one...
Here we go!
Ready, Pappa!
Yes! That's what I'm talking about!
Yes!
I made a mistake.
Hey, me too.
I made a few mistakes.
Greatly, greatly, greatly
Yes, yes...
It's a little bit difficult...
It's a little difficult, isn't it?
Watch this video.
If you watch this video, remember it, and perform it live...
I think you will enjoy it many times more.
Please watch this video and try to memorize it!
We are already doing the spring tour.
Yes, that's right.
Well, some of you are already doing it.
I see.
There are people who are doing it.
I hope we can all get together and make it happen!
Please give it a try, everyone!
Please do!
Let's have fun together, inferential aliens!
Thank you very much!